<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>The Journeys We Take</title>
  <!--<link>https://www.jencraigevans.com</link>-->
  <description>The Journeys We Take. A Podcast by Jen Craig-Evans</description>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>Trailer</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/podcast-intro_202010/Podcast%20Intro.mp3</link>
    <description>The Journeys We Take Podcast Trailer/Introduction</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">070f6875-d0da-4ded-98ea-198701855c3b</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E001 Origin Story</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/origin-story-complete/Origin%20Story%20%28Complete%29.mp3</link>
    <description>This is the origin story of the podcast; that is how I have come to find myself sitting on the floor of a closet, with an old foam mattress topper wrapped around me, speaking into the ether of a microphone with who knows who on the other end.

In this episode, I share with you how the podcast was born out of a strange calling during an exquisitely challenging time; right in the middle of our collective chaos that was 2020.

Podcast Music by my dear friend Justin Barnard
https://www.instagram.com/justinvolution/

Sound Engineering done by the talented Adnan Coban 
https://www.instagram.com/aceymusic/</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">de9f0259-7c36-46c0-ad1a-5fa0caeb2562</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E002 Sam Streeter</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-002-sam-streeter/Sam%20Streeter.mp3</link>
    <description>In this episode I have the honour and pleasure of chatting with Sam Streeter.
Sam has recently put her role as a yoga/ meditation teacher and mentor on hold to be a full time new mama. 
For well over a decade she has dived into deep self work, exploration and life experiences; discovering new layers herself all along the way. Sam says she thrives and feels most purposeful in community. She has designed a chosen family with her closest friends who share the same core values of communication, vulnerability, honesty, support, and a willingness to change. 

We talk about dysfunctional family dynamics, rebellion, abuse, grief, mental health, the journey of self discovery, love, pregnancy through a pandemic and how life has come full circle.

Connect with Sam on Instagram @_samstreeter</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">4a20e5c1-2be7-4936-b853-346d744f1a72</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E003 Soniko Waira</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-003-soniko-waira/E003%20Soniko%20Waira.mp3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[In this Episode, I have the pleasure of speaking with Soniko Waira. Soniko was born  in the city of Kitu, Ecuador. He'll tell you that growing up in a city of 3 million people led him to a loneliness and disconnection from nature.
During his time living in this city, he was deeply drawn to the arts culture, leading him to his first love of and self immersion in music. For a time, he participated in the party scene, which we talk about, before he realized he was being called to live another way.


He describes himself as a musician, artist and visionary. Currently, his work is taking him all over the world where he meets with many wise elders from different indigenous cultures. Upon moving to Canada several years back, he spent time with the Sinixt people on their traditional territory, commonly known as the 'Slocan Valley' here in the Kootenays of British Columbia.


We talk a fair bit about this time he spent with this community, including his invitation to live with them for a year and his key take aways by way of lessons learned. And we go on to chat about how this has informed his work as a spiritual teacher and creator of his work called the Heart Map Experience. He shares this work in the form of workshops, ceremonies, and vision quests.


You connect with Soniko, his music and his work through the following:


website: www.heartmapexperience.org
Facebook: www.facebook.com/sonikomusica
Instagram: www.instagram.com/soniko_w
Music: www.soundcloud.com/soniko_w]]></description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">ad18dfb6-fdbf-4cf8-bb43-078691e265d8</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E004 Sara Braidwood</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/sara-braidwood/Sara%20Braidwood.mp3</link>
    <description>Sara's story is potent, powerful and inspiring.
In her recently published book, Rewild Her, she explores the pain, loneliness and potency of her journey that has led her here.

In this episode, we chat about her journey thus far. We explore the topic of loss, grief, domestic violence, addiction, and the human experience that is seeking relief from our pain. She gets very raw and openly shares about this period of her life in detail, giving the listener a glimpse into the world of deep pain, but also the real and powerful possibly of what can be on the other side.

Today, Sara is doing powerful work as a Life Coach and is a budding author with a very important story to share.

You can connect with Sara on Instagram:
https://instagram.com/re.wildco?igshid=mxzq2i704q87

And you can find her professional offerings as well as her book, Rewild Her, here:
https://www.rewildco.ca/</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">66993c3f-0dbe-44cc-9f3e-43929bb120c3</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 7 Feb 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  
   <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E005 Ned Burwell on Tattooing, Overcoming Dark Mental Health Times and Love</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-005-ned-burwell-on-tattooing-overcoming-darkness-and-being-love/E005%20Ned%20Burwell%20on%20Tattooing%2C%20Overcoming%20Darkness%20and%20Being%20Love.mp3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[I met Ned just over ten years ago. My mother had just passed away. I wanted a tattoo that I had been arguing with my mum about from her perspective as a public health nurse. And so after she passed, my mum's good friend introduced me to Ned. It was a healing experience unlike any other, and I now have a full upper back and good chunk of both arms inked at Ned's hand. I have had the honour of listening to many of his stories in my hours spent in his tattoo chair, and I am so excited to share many of them with you here now.

In this episode, we discuss Ned's journey through life up until now; his struggles, his dark and challenging mental health times in which he shares feeling suicidal, the support he received and sought out, and the other side on which he has found himself for many years now. He is an incredible, self-made tattoo artist and mental health advocate. He does so much for his community through mental health advocacy, fundraising, education through his three published books, and his work with U Matter.

Ned has devoted the last 20 years of his life studying spirituality and self help. He spent eight years with the Ishaya Monks, eventually he took vows and became a monk for one year. For the last 27 years he has been a self-employed tattoo artist. His experience as an artist spurred his awakening and his time with the monks helped deepen it. Ned's curious spirit and willingness to love has enlivened his ability to be a teacher to many. 
Ned attended the University of Western Ontario to study Psychology and English. Over the years he has facilitated workshops and talks in schools, the Canadian Mental Health Association, Ontario Police Collage, Rogers Daytime TV, Unifor 2017 EFAP/Addictions Conference. In 2016, he became an Ordained Minister.

Currently, he is extra busy creating extra resources for his Umatter site, including free, full access to the audiobook version of Be Love. He says, 'This is a notable time where we need to come together and lend support wherever we can. There has never been a more critical moment in our history where we need as many conscious people as possible. The darkness the world is experiencing is a great call for us to reach into our soul and to unify with others. It is my aim to create heartfelt connections with others and to support the personal empowerment of all beings. Your empowerment and deeper awakenings will not only give this planet hope, but it will also assist others to rise to their greatest potential.' 

Connect with Ned on Instagram:
https://www.instagram.com/nedburwell/

or on his Websites for his other content:
www.umatter.ca 
www.endlessboundaries.ca]]></description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">6290664b-ace8-4c34-a54c-a20b586ed105</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E006 Salwa Kyobe on Belonging, Rock Bottoms and Coming Home</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-006-salwa-kyobe/E006%20Salwa%20Kyobe.mp3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[We find ourselves collectively in a time of isolation; both literally from other humans and more existentially as it relates to belonging. 
This episode with Salwa was timely as it relates to the above in that one of the greatest themes we discuss is just that; Belonging.

Salwa shares her story and journey up until now, which includes her family coming to the United States from Uganda when she was three years old (ish). She talks about her memories as a black child going to school in a predominately white neighbourhood and school, as her family settled in Seattle. We talk about her experience of feeling 'other' and how that shaped the way she found herself showing in the world as she grew up. 

Salwa shares her insight around her personal rock bottom and feeling disconnected from herself and her emotional expression. She speaks to her journey from that moment of clarity, to all of the tools she has learned to cultivate along the way; leading to what she refers to as entering a new season of life to embody her truth and speak boldly.

We talk about how deeply impactful it was for her to return to her birth place in Uganda in 2018, and how re-learning to speak and write in her native language has provided a bridge to deeper connectedness and belonging.

Salwa is a TBM coach who specializes in identifying and excavating the truth from our own personal shadows, especially the aspects of ourselves we don't want to look at.

You can connect with Salwa on Instagram:
https://www.instagram.com/salwa.yazmin/
Or to book a session: https://tobemagnetic.com/coaching-with-salwa]]></description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">e2dc7afc-243f-411d-a118-b0fed836edf1</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  
</channel>

</rss>
