<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>The Journeys We Take</title>
  <!--<link>https://www.jencraigevans.com</link>-->
  <description>The Journeys We Take. A Podcast by Jen Craig-Evans</description>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>Trailer</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/podcast-intro_202010/Podcast%20Intro.mp3</link>
    <description>The Journeys We Take Podcast Trailer/Introduction</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">070f6875-d0da-4ded-98ea-198701855c3b</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E001 Origin Story</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/origin-story-complete/Origin%20Story%20%28Complete%29.mp3</link>
    <description>This is the origin story of the podcast; that is how I have come to find myself sitting on the floor of a closet, with an old foam mattress topper wrapped around me, speaking into the ether of a microphone with who knows who on the other end.

In this episode, I share with you how the podcast was born out of a strange calling during an exquisitely challenging time; right in the middle of our collective chaos that was 2020.

Podcast Music by my dear friend Justin Barnard
https://www.instagram.com/justinvolution/

Sound Engineering done by the talented Adnan Coban 
https://www.instagram.com/aceymusic/</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">de9f0259-7c36-46c0-ad1a-5fa0caeb2562</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E002 Sam Streeter</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-002-sam-streeter/Sam%20Streeter.mp3</link>
    <description>In this episode I have the honour and pleasure of chatting with Sam Streeter.
Sam has recently put her role as a yoga/ meditation teacher and mentor on hold to be a full time new mama. 
For well over a decade she has dived into deep self work, exploration and life experiences; discovering new layers herself all along the way. Sam says she thrives and feels most purposeful in community. She has designed a chosen family with her closest friends who share the same core values of communication, vulnerability, honesty, support, and a willingness to change. 

We talk about dysfunctional family dynamics, rebellion, abuse, grief, mental health, the journey of self discovery, love, pregnancy through a pandemic and how life has come full circle.

Connect with Sam on Instagram @_samstreeter</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">4a20e5c1-2be7-4936-b853-346d744f1a72</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E003 Soniko Waira</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/e-003-soniko-waira/E003%20Soniko%20Waira.mp3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[In this Episode, I have the pleasure of speaking with Soniko Waira. Soniko was born  in the city of Kitu, Ecuador. He'll tell you that growing up in a city of 3 million people led him to a loneliness and disconnection from nature.
During his time living in this city, he was deeply drawn to the arts culture, leading him to his first love of and self immersion in music. For a time, he participated in the party scene, which we talk about, before he realized he was being called to live another way.


He describes himself as a musician, artist and visionary. Currently, his work is taking him all over the world where he meets with many wise elders from different indigenous cultures. Upon moving to Canada several years back, he spent time with the Sinixt people on their traditional territory, commonly known as the 'Slocan Valley' here in the Kootenays of British Columbia.


We talk a fair bit about this time he spent with this community, including his invitation to live with them for a year and his key take aways by way of lessons learned. And we go on to chat about how this has informed his work as a spiritual teacher and creator of his work called the Heart Map Experience. He shares this work in the form of workshops, ceremonies, and vision quests.


You connect with Soniko, his music and his work through the following:


website: www.heartmapexperience.org
Facebook: www.facebook.com/sonikomusica
Instagram: www.instagram.com/soniko_w
Music: www.soundcloud.com/soniko_w]]></description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">ad18dfb6-fdbf-4cf8-bb43-078691e265d8</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <author>jen@jencraigevans.com</author>
    <title>E004 with Sara Braidwood</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/download/sara-braidwood/Sara%20Braidwood.mp3</link>
    <description>Sara's story is potent, powerful and inspiring.
In her recently published book, Rewild Her, she explores the pain, loneliness and potency of her journey that has led her here.

In this episode, we chat about her journey thus far. We explore the topic of loss, grief, domestic violence, addiction, and the human experience that is seeking relief from our pain. She gets very raw and openly shares about this period of her life in detail, giving the listener a glimpse into the world of deep pain, but also the real and powerful possibly of what can be on the other side.

Today, Sara is doing powerful work as a Life Coach and is a budding author with a very important story to share.

You can connect with Sara on Instagram:
https://instagram.com/re.wildco?igshid=mxzq2i704q87

And you can find her professional offerings as well as her book, Rewild Her, here:
https://www.rewildco.ca/</description>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">66993c3f-0dbe-44cc-9f3e-43929bb120c3</guid>
    <pubDate>Sun, 7 Feb 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
  </item>
  
  
</channel>

</rss>
